We're going to do another exercise of sentence
completion and short answer questions in section three.
In this exercise, based on the questions, you
can see that there will be two speakers
in the recording, including Anna and David.
One can be a teacher and one can
be a student.
Now let's take a look at how to
do this exercise.
In questions one to three, you are allowed
to write one word only.
Here are the key words in these questions.
And these are the type of information that
you may need to find for each blank.
In questions four to eight, you are allowed
to write a maximum of three words and
a number.
And the shortest answer will be one word
or a number.
Let's practice predicting the type of information for
these questions.
Nice job!
Now we're going to listen and find the
answers to all these questions in the practice
section.
Remember that for section three, you should take
notes using a table for two speakers.
And don't forget to listen actively and check
your answers at the end.